Terror is ready to strike!
Sssssss is a horror, science fiction film directed by Bernard L. Kowalski.
David, a college student, is looking for a job.
He is hired by Dr.
Stoner as a lab assistant for his research and experiments on snakes.
David also begins to fall for Stoner's young daughter, Kristina.
However, the good doctor has secretly brewed up a serum that can transform any
man into a King Cobra snake-and he plans to use it on David.
Dr. Carl Stoner, played by Strother Martin.
David Blake, played by Dirk Benedict.
Kristina Stoner, played by Heather Menzies.
Dr. Ken Daniels, played by Richard B. Shull.
Kogen, played by Tim O'Connor.
Sheriff Dale Hardison, played by Jack Ging.
Sssssss is a 1973 American body horror film directed by Bernard L.
Kowalski and starring Strother Martin, Dirk Benedict, and Heather Menzies.
Its plot follows a college student who becomes a laboratory assistant to a herpetologist who
is covertly developing a serum that can transform human beings into snakes.
The make-up effects were created by John Chambers and Nick Marcellino.
It received a nomination for the Best Science Fiction Film award of the
Academy of Science Fiction, Fantasy and Horror Films in 1975.
The film explores themes of experiment, snake,
transformation, mad scientist, turns into animal.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.